eurasianet.org 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Eurasianet

**Eurasianet Privacy Policy and Terms of Use**

Eurasianet offers free use of our news website with the assurance of unmonitored and private browsing. We collect only two types of information about our readers: a name and email address for our newsletter, and aggregate statistical data about website usage. 

If you wish to receive our **weekly email** , you may voluntarily [subscribe](https://eurasianet.us12.list-manage.com/subscribe?u=3602b0fdfe153be0a50ebcf9c&id=ae81697832) with your name and email address at the provided link or on our [homepage](https://eurasianet.org/). We do not share this information with, nor would we ever sell it to, any third party. Additionally, your information is not shared among Eurasianet staff except in the creation and distribution of this email. You may unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time by following the directions in the footer of the email. Should you experience problems, please contact Digital Content Editor Maria Mammina at [mammina@eurasianet.org](mailto:mammina@eurasianet.org).

To provide excellent news and user experience on our site, **** we **** collect **aggregate, anonymized statistical data** that tracks website usage, such as what articles are most popular, how many readers visit the site, and the period of time readers spend on the site, among other data points. This information is gathered through the use of a standard browser feature called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on a website visitor’s hard drive to help us identify repeat visitors to our site and track the interests of our users to enhance our coverage and your experience on the site. Usage of a cookie is not in any way linked to personally identifiable information our site. Eurasianet is the sole owner of this data and will not share with any third party outside of our organization; the data collected is used solely to improve Eurasianet.

Disclaimer: Our articles sometimes include **external links** , such as government websites, other news outlets, and research institutions, etc. We cannot guarantee these websites adhere to our privacy policy. Please note that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites, and we encourage our readers to be aware they have left [Eurasianet.org](https://eurasianet.org/) and to read the privacy statements of any other website.    

Should you have questions or require further information, please contact Digital Content Editor Maria Mammina at [mammina@eurasianet.org](mailto:mammina@eurasianet.org).
